<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>[MLP] My Little RimPony</name>
	<author>GeodesicDragon</author>
	<packageId>geodesicdragon.rimpony</packageId>
	<url>https://discord.gg/BGKnpza</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description><![CDATA[<b>ABOUT</b>

It has been thousands of years since <i>My Little Pony: Friendship is Magic</i> last aired, but the show is once again enjoying a resurgence; how it came to the rim, though, remains a mystery. Regardless of the hows and whys, many colonists have embraced the show, as the colourful characters and messages of peace, hope and friendship help them to escape the struggles of trying to survive daily life in their colonies.

Many of them have even taken to carrying pony plushies, with some people claiming that they feel as though the object is transferring some of the essence of that particular pony into them. While no scientific proof as been found of this, many people are accepting it as fact because it gives them something to be happy about. Consequently, pony plushies are now as much a part of everyday rim life as food and guns.

<b>IDEOLOGY EXPANSION</b>

I've created a new mod that adds items related to the Ideology DLC.

STEAM: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2684300411
GITHUB: https://github.com/GeodesicDragon/mlrp-ideology

<b>WHAT DOES THIS MOD DO?</b>

1. Adds plush versions of a variety of ponies, each of which can be carried in the utility slot to confer bonuses depending on which pony it is. It also adds my OC, because I <i>did</i> make the mod after all. :P
2. Adds the Elements of Harmony, made by combining one of each Mane Six plush with 100 gold. This item confers the bonuses of all Mane Six plushies at once.
3. Adds a pila-based weapon which hurls Cadences at your enemy. This 'wife thrower' has the same stats as a pila, though it can be thrown a bit quicker; it requires skill 3 Crafting, a Cadence plush and 100 wood to make.
4. All items added by this mod are made at a dedicated plushie bench using 300 cloth and and have a market value of 200 silver.
5. Adds a secret item only available through quests or traders.
6. Adds the 'Brony' trait, which renders the pawn incapable of violence, but increases their Social skill by 6 and prevents mood loss from being insulted.
7. Adds the 'Brony Community' scenario, which starts you with three pawns, each of whom has the Brony trait. You start with four ready to install steel mini-turrets, as well as the necessary research to build more.

Colonists will equip plushies themselves, though you might need to force them to wear the one that actually suits them better.

<b>BONUSES GIVEN</b>

Applejack: +15% to plant work speed and harvest yield.
Big Macintosh: +25kg to maximum carry capacity.
Cheerilee: +50% to global learning factor.
Discord: +25% global work speed.
Fluttershy: +15% each to animal tame chance and training chance.
Izzy Moonbow: +10 to mood and opinions of others boosted by 10%.
Pinkie Pie: +20% to social impact.
Nurse Haywick (my OC): +15% each to medical tend speed and quality.
Rainbow Dash: +50% to movement and +5% to melee hit chance and shooting accuracy.
Rarity: +20% to trade price improvement.
Princess Cadence: +20% to pain shock threshold.
Princess Celestia: -20% to mental break threshold.
Princess Luna: +50% to rest multiplier (for faster sleep).
Starlight Glimmer: -50% to psychic sensitivity.
Twilight Sparkle: +20% research speed.

<b>CAN YOU ADD *CHARACTER* TO THIS?</b>

If you have any suggestions about what bonus(es) they could give then sure, I'll consider it. Let me know via my Discord server.

<b>ART CREDITS</b>

All art was sourced from Derpibooru and is used with permission - usually obtained from the description on the piece - or under a Creative Commons Attribution-Noncommercial-No Derivative Works 3.0 License where possible; credit is followed by the image ID.

Applejack: CindyDreamLight (2450572)
Big Macintosh: dashiesparkle* (1167810)
Cheerilee: juniberries (2527617)
Discord: chrzanek97* (2584926)
Fluttershy: RainbowCrab (2508169)
Nurse Haywick: GraphiteSketch AKA Timsplosion (1852562)
Izzy Moonbow (plush): inaactive (2561243)
Izzy Moonbow (smoke launcher): ejlightning007arts (2718787)
Pinkie Pie: flizzick (2490254)
Princess Cadence: Unknown Artist (2115510)
Princess Celestia: killagouge* (2058026)
Princess Luna: chrzanek97 (2124813)
Rainbow Dash: TheMightyShizam* (2501021)
Rarity: MoongazePonies (2503325)
Starlight Glimmer: zacatron94* (1426211)
Twilight Sparkle: andoanimalia (2521465)
Elements of Harmony: spiritofthwwolf* (sic) (63922)

<i>PROJECTILES</i>

Rainbow Laser: Made by me.
Tennis ball: Taken from art by greenhoof (2560819)

* Permission could not be sought from this person; should they get in touch with a request to remove the image, I will gladly comply.

<b>I HAVE A QUESTION/COMMENT/BUG/SUGGESTION</b>

Please use my Discord server - https://discord.gg/BGKnpza - for all enquiries; I am on Discord a lot, so I will reply to you a lot faster than I will via a comment on the Workshop.]]></description>
</ModMetaData>