<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>[MLP] My Little RimPony</name>
	<author>GeodesicDragon</author>
	<packageId>geodesicdragon.rimpony</packageId>
	<url>https://discord.gg/BGKnpza</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<loadBefore>
		<li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
		<li>geodesicdragon.rimpony.cepatch</li>
	</loadBefore>
	<description><![CDATA[<b>ABOUT</b>

It has been thousands of years since <i>My Little Pony: Friendship is Magic</i> last aired, but the show is once again enjoying a resurgence; how it came to the rim, though, remains a mystery. Regardless of the hows and whys, many colonists have embraced the show, as the colourful characters and messages of peace, hope and friendship help them to escape the struggles of trying to survive daily life in their colonies.

Many of them have even taken to carrying pony plushies, with some people claiming that they feel as though the object is transferring some of the essence of that particular pony into them. While no scientific proof as been found of this, many people are accepting it as fact simply because it gives them something to be happy about. Consequently, pony plushies are now as much a part of everyday rim life as food and guns.

<b>IDEOLOGY EXPANSION</b>

I've created a new mod that adds items related to the Ideology DLC.

STEAM: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2684300411
GITHUB: https://github.com/GeodesicDragon/mlrp-ideology

<b>COMBAT EXTENDED PATCH</b>

Yes, one exists now.

STEAM: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2726060046
GITHUB: https://github.com/GeodesicDragon/mlrp-cepatch/releases

<b>I HAVE A QUESTION/COMMENT/BUG/SUGGESTION</b>

Please use my Discord server - https://discord.gg/BGKnpza - for all enquiries; I am on Discord a lot, so I will reply to you a lot faster than I will via a comment on the Workshop.

More details can be found in the About.txt and Credits.txt files, located in the About folder.]]></description>
</ModMetaData>