<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>[MLP] My Little RimPony</name>
	<author>GeodesicDragon</author>
	<packageId>geodesicdragon.rimpony</packageId>
	<url>https://discord.gg/BGKnpza</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description><![CDATA[<b>ABOUT</b>

It has been thousands of years since <i>My Little Pony: Friendship is Magic</i> last aired, but the show is once again enjoying a resurgence; how it came to the rim, though, remains a mystery. Regardless of the hows and whys, many residents have embraced the show, as the colourful characters and messages of peace, hope and friendship help them to escape the struggles of trying to survive daily life in their colonies. Many of them have taken to carrying plushies of the main characters with them, with some even claiming that they feel as though a part of the character lives within the plush, which is then transferred to them.

The craze quickly caught on, and pony plushies are now as much a part of everyday rim life as food and guns.

<b>WHAT DOES THIS MOD DO?</b>

This mod adds plush versions of Celestia, Luna, the Mane Six, and my OC - because why not - which can be carried in the utility slot to confer bonuses depending on which pony it is. They are made at a tailoring bench using 300 cloth and and have a market value of 500 silver.

You will have to force colonists to equip the item, as they will not do it themselves.

<b>BONUSES GIVEN</b>

Applejack: +10% to plant work speed and harvest yield.
Fluttershy: +10% to animal tame chance and training chance.
Pinkie Pie: +10% to social impact and trade price improvement.
Rainbow Dash: +10% to movement and +5% to melee hit chance and shooting accuracy.
Rarity: +10% to mining speed, +5 to pawn beauty, and +5% to trade price improvement.
Twilight Sparkle: +20% research speed.

Princess Celestia: -20% to mental break threshold.
Princess Luna: +20% to rest multiplier (for faster sleep).

Nurse Haywick (my OC): +20% to medical tend speed.

<b>CAN YOU ADD *CHARACTER* TO THIS?</b>

Sorry, but no; as much as I would love to add other characters, I don't want to clog the game with loads of new items. Plus, I'd have a hard time figuring out what bonuses each character could give. If you have any suggestions, though, then by all means tell me!

<b>ART CREDITS</b>

All art was sourced from Derpibooru and is used with permission or under a Creative Commons Attribution-Noncommercial-No Derivative Works 3.0 License where possible; credit is followed by the image ID.

Applejack: CindyDreamLight (2450572)
Fluttershy: RainbowCrab (2508169)
Pinkie Pie: flizzick (2490254)
Rainbow Dash: TheMightyShizam* (2501021)
Rarity: MoongazePonies (2503325)
Twilight Sparkle: andoanimalia (2521465)

Celestia: killagouge* (2058026)
Luna: chrzanek97 (2124813)

Haywick: GraphiteSketch AKA Timsplosion (1852562)

* This person has been inactive for a while, meaning permission could not be sought; if you are this person and want me to remove the image, then get in touch and I will gladly comply.

<b>I HAVE A QUESTION/COMMENT/BUG/SUGGESTION</b>

Please use my Discord server - https://discord.gg/BGKnpza - for all enquiries; I am on Discord a lot, and will reply to you a lot faster than I will via a comment on the Workshop.]]></description>
</ModMetaData>