<Defs>

<TipSetDef>
	<defName>MyLittleRimPony_Tips</defName>
	<tips>
		<li TKey="PlushieTrader">Plushie traders can be requested from most factions via the comms console.</li>
		<li TKey="OFCWeapon">The Orbital Friendship Cannon can be rearmed using 100 gold.</li>
		<li TKey="WifeThrower">The wife thrower has slightly better long range accuracy than a pila, and can be thrown twice as fast.</li>
		<li TKey="Celestia">The Celestia plush can be used to counteract the effects of the 'nervous' and 'volatile' traits.</li>
		<li TKey="Cadence">The Cadence plush can be used to counteract the effect of the 'wimp' trait.</li>
		<li TKey="Luna">Giving a Luna plush to a pawn with the 'quick sleeper' trait will make them rest twice as fast.</li>
		<li TKey="Cheerilee">Giving a Cheerilee plush to a pawn with the 'fast learner' trait will help them improve their skills faster.</li>
		<li TKey="Starlight">Giving a Starlight Glimmer plush to a pawn with the 'psychically hypersensitive' or 'psychically sensitive' traits will lower - or even eliminate - the mood penalty from psychic drones.</li>
		<li TKey="SweetieBelle">Giving a Sweetie Belle plush to a pawn with low Cooking skill will slightly reduce the chance of them poisoning meals.</li>
		<li TKey="Screwball">Screwball generators can be built from pretty much any material, including wood.</li>
		<li TKey="DiscordLamp">Since Discord lamps don't require power, they are able to continue providing light during solar flares.</li>
		<li TKey="XMLExtensions">If you have the XML Extensions mod enabled, you can configure many parts of this mod to your liking, such as whether or not bronies can be violent and how many textiles you need to craft plushies.</li>
		<li TKey="NurseRedheart">Nurse Redheart will spawn medicine as long as she has enough power.</li>
		<li TKey="SSCS6K">The Super Speedy Cider Squeezy 6000 will spawn beer as long as it has enough power.</li>
		<li TKey="AggroTurrets">Mudbriar, Quibble Pants and Zephyr Breeze turrets do no damage, but can help to distract raiders. They are, however, quite expensive to build.</li>
		<li TKey="Fleur">The Fleur de Lis plush can be used to counter the effects of the 'ugly' traits.</li>
		<li TKey="NightmareMoon">The Nightmare Moon statue allows you to acquire many exotic items using silver, which is handy if your colonists lack the skills, though it does work out to be more expensive than acquiring them normally.</li>
		<li TKey="DaybreakerOne">The Daybreaker statue allows you to convert steel, plasteel, uranium, jade and gold into silver, and vice versa.</li>
		<li TKey="DaybreakerTwo">The Daybreaker statue allows you to create regular and advanced components much faster than using a fabrication bench, once the relevant research has been completed.</li>
		<li TKey="PoisonJokeEffect">Poison joke will affect a pawns consciousness, moving, manipulation, talking, eating, sight, hearing or breathing in either a positive or negative way.</li>
		<li TKey="PoisonJokeCutiePox">Poison joke has a chance of inflicting a pawn with the Cutie Pox.</li>
	</tips>
</TipSetDef>

</Defs>