<Defs>

<TipSetDef>
	<defName>MyLittleRimPony_Tips</defName>
	<tips>
		<li>Apple Bloom: "I WANT IT NOOOOW!"</li>
		<li>Applejack: "How do ya like them apples?"</li>
		<li>Big Macintosh: "Eeyup."</li>
		<li>Cheerilee: "Yes I know, but honestly, that's how everypony was wearing their mane back then."</li>
		<li>Daring Do: "Another day, another dungeon!"</li>
		<li>Daybreaker: "Ugh. So much black. We get it. You're sad."</li>
		<li>Discord: "Make sense? Oh, what fun is there in making sense?"</li>
		<li>Fleur de Lis: "Mmm! A pony with expensive tastes, I see."</li>
		<li>Fluttershy: "You're going to LOVE ME!"</li>
		<li>Maud Pie: "You're the most basic of jokes."</li>
		<li>Mudbriar: "I will not apologize for speaking with precision."</li>
		<li>Nightmare Moon: "You're kidding. You're kidding, right?"</li>
		<li>Nurse Haywick: "I hope you're not expecting a quote."</li>
		<li>Nurse Redheart: "Shhh."</li>
		<li>Izzy Moonbow: "Hi, new friend!"</li>
		<li>Pinkie Pie: "Eternal chaos comes with chocolate rain, you guys! CHOCOLATE RAIN!"</li>
		<li>Princess Cadence: "One of these days we need to get together when the fate of Equestria isn't hanging in the balance."</li>
		<li>Princess Celestia: "Hmm. I was not aware that I was an expression. An appropriate one, of course, for even I don't know the answers."</li>
		<li>Princess Luna: "The fun has been doubled!"</li>
		<li>Quibble Pants: "Now this is something that only a true fan can appreciate."</li>
		<li>Rainbow Dash: "It needs to be about 20% cooler."</li>
		<li>Rarity: "Of all the things that could have happened, this is the WORST. POSSIBLE. THING."</li>
		<li>Scootaloo: "What are you, a dictionary?"</li>
		<li>Shining Armour: "Come on, gang! Are we gonna gallop, or are we gonna trot?!"</li>
		<li>Spoiled Rich: "Honestly, if you're looking for somepony to fund-raise, I can bring in enough bits to have several buildings named after me."</li>
		<li>Starlight Glimmer: "PHYLLIS, NO!"</li>
		<li>Sunset Shimmer: "Am I the only one who thinks this is overkill?"</li>
		<li>Sweetie Belle: "OH, COME ON!"</li>
		<li>Sweetie Bot: "If this world isn't going to love me, I'll teach it to FEAR ME instead."</li>
		<li>Twilight Sparkle: "I have to finish this report to the princess summarizing all my other reports to the princess."</li>
		<li>Zephyr Breeze: "To be fair, it was never made specifically clear to me what 'guarding' actually means, so this is on you."</li>
		<li>Plushie traders can be requested from tribal, outlander and imperial factions via the comms console.</li>
		<li>The Orbital Friendship Cannon can be rearmed using 100 gold.</li>
		<li>The wife thrower has slightly better long range accuracy than a pila, but can be thrown twice as fast.</li>
		<li>The Celestia plush can be used to counteract the effects of the 'nervous' and 'volatile' traits.</li>
		<li Name="PrincessCadence">The Cadence plush can be used to slightly counteract the effect of the 'wimp' trait.</li>
		<li>Giving a Luna plush to a pawn with the 'quick sleeper' trait will make them rest twice as fast.</li>
		<li>Giving a Cheerilee plush to a pawn with the 'fast learner' trait will help them improve their skills faster.</li>
		<li>Giving a Starlight Glimmer plush to a pawn with the 'psychically hypersensitive' or 'psychically sensitive' traits will lower - or even eliminate - the mood penalty from psychic drones.</li>
		<li>Giving a Sweetie Belle plush to a pawn with low Cooking skill should reduce the chance of your other pawns suffering food poisoning.</li>
		<li>Building Screwball generators only requires textiles, which makes them ideal for powering your deep mining drills.</li>
		<li>Since Discord lamps don't require power, they are able to continue providing light during solar flares.</li>
		<li>If you have the XML Extensions mod enabled, you can configure many parts of this mod to your liking, such as whether or not bronies can be violent and how many textiles you need to craft plushies.</li>
		<li Name="NurseRedheart">Nurse Redheart is a rare reward from quests; she will grant you 5 Medicine every 10 days as long as she has 350W of power.</li>
		<li Name="SSCS6K">The Super Speedy Cider Squeezy 6000 is a rare reward from quests; it will grant you 30 Beer every 30 days as long as it has 500W of power.</li>
		<li>Mudbriar, Quibble Pants and Zephyr Breeze turrets do no damage, but can help to distract raiders. They are, however, quite expensive to build.</li>
		<li>The Fleur de Lis plush can be used to counter the effects of the 'ugly' traits.</li>
		<li>The Nightmare Moon statue lets you acquire many exotic items using chocolate, which is handy if your colonists lack the skills, though it does work out to be more expensive than acquiring them normally.</li>
		<li>The Daybreaker statue lets you convert 100 steel, plasteel, uranium, jade or gold into the market value equivalent of another. She will also let you create components (regular and advanced) much faster than using a fabrication bench, but bear in mind that chemfuel is required for everything she does.</li>
	</tips>
</TipSetDef>

</Defs>