<Defs>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="MLRP_UpdateNewsBase">
		<defName>MLRP_UpdateNews</defName>
		<modNameReadable>[MLP] My Little RimPony</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>geodesicdragon.rimpony</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://discord.gg/BGKnpza</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="MLRP_UpdateNewsBase">
		<defName>MLRP_Version_600</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>6.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;WHAT'S NEW?&lt;/b&gt;\n\nThe mod is now available in French.\n\n- Core: Support for RimWorld 1.4 has been removed.\n- Core: You can now request reinforced barrels from Nightmare Moon once you research mortars.\n- Core: Enemies now have a chance to drop ruined plushies, which you can recycle at the plushie bench to get some materials.\n- Core: Nightmare Moon is no longer accepting item returns.\n- Core: Once you've researched brewing, Daybreaker will be able to help you make wort.\n- Biotech: The Diamond Dogs have learned archery.\n- Anomaly: Thingpone recipes now require twisted meat as well as silver.\n- Ponies of the Rim: Ponies will no longer spawn with the xenotypes and/or genes added by My Little RimPony.\n\nRefer to the changelog for full details on all the changes! (There's a lot.)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="MLRP_UpdateNewsBase">
		<defName>MLRP_Version_51539</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.15.39</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;WHAT'S NEW?&lt;/b&gt;\n\n- Core: You can now request 50 units of herbal medicine from Nightmare Moon in exchange for 250 units of (vegetarian) food.\n- Anomaly: Added Thingpone. This adorable eldritch horror will offer you items from beyond the void in exchange for silver (and, in one case, twisted meat).\n- Anomaly: You can now purchase dread leather from the Fabric Exchange.\n- Anomaly: Added two new recipes to the Daybreaker statue, allowing you to convert silver to bioferrite and vice versa.\n\nPlease refer to the changelog for more info!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="MLRP_UpdateNewsBase">
		<defName>MLRP_Version_445109</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.45.109</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;WHAT'S NEW?&lt;/b&gt;\n\n- Core: Added Miss Harshwhinny, a passive cooler that can freeze a room at twice the fuel cost\n- Biotech: Added the Renegade Alicorn scenario\n\n&lt;b&gt;WHAT'S CHANGED?&lt;/b&gt;\n\n- Core: Poison joke plants now require 70% soil fertility (was 140%)\n- Core: Doubled the hitpoints of Screwballs\n\nPlease refer to the changelog for more info!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="MLRP_UpdateNewsBase">
		<defName>MLRP_Version_43398</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.33.98</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;WHAT'S NEW?&lt;/b&gt;\n\n- Biotech: Added the batpony xenotype and faction (requires Alpha Genes)\n- Removed many of the conversion recipes from the Daybreaker statue\n- Reduced combat power of NPC faction pawns to hopefully allow more to spawn during raids or other events\n\nPlease refer to the changelog for more info!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="MLRP_UpdateNewsBase">
		<defName>MLRP_Version_41738</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.17.38</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;WHAT'S NEW?&lt;/b&gt;\n\n- Added a bunch of recipes to the Daybreaker statue which allow you to synthesise drugs in batches of 100, using half the regular amount of chemfuel\n- Biotech: Added the Diamond Dog xenotype and faction\n\nPlease refer to the changelog for more info!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="MLRP_UpdateNewsBase">
		<defName>MLRP_Version_4431</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.4.31</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;WHAT'S NEW?&lt;/b&gt;\n\n- New Storyteller: Sunny Starscout (more friends and less enemies)\n- Biotech: The Brony Xenotypes scenario now includes a changeling\n- All of the pony xenotypes now get along with each other\n- Changelings can now come in a variety of colours\n- Poison joke now has a chance of giving pawns the Cutie Pox\n- Added Alpha genes patch for alicorns and pegasi which will give newly spawned ones a shiny pair of wings\n\nPlease refer to the changelog for more info!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="MLRP_UpdateNewsBase">
		<defName>MLRP_Version_417</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.1.7</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;WHAT'S NEW?&lt;/b&gt;\n\nThe Changeling xenotype has been added.\n* Acid Spray\n* High cold resistance\n* Pyrophobia\n* High libido\n* Fertile\n* Very ugly\n* Grey eyes\n* Bald\n* No beard\n* Insect voice\n* Facial ridges\n* Ink black skin\n* Robust digestion\n* Pollution stimulus\n* Great construction skill\n* Great crafting skill\n* Terrible mining skill\n* Terrible cooking skill\n* Terrible plants skill\n* Terrible animals skill\n* Terrible artistic skill\n* Terrible medicine skill\n* Terrible social skill\n* Terrible intellectual skill</content></HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="MLRP_UpdateNewsBase">
		<defName>MLRP_Version_400</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>&lt;b&gt;Welcome to the Xenotypes Update!&lt;/b&gt;\n\n&lt;i&gt;What's New?&lt;/i&gt;\n\n- New Building: Marble Pie's Rock Exchange\n- Plushies now have their own item slot\n- Biotech: Four new pony based xenotypes\n- Biotech: New xenotypes scenario</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
</Defs>